A Finding Aid to the Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson Papers, 1833-1980 (bulk 1900-1980), in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Andrew Dasburg Papers, circa 1900-1980; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 6 Linear feet Box 1-6
  - Correspondence, circa 1906-1979; 1.2; Archival Resource Key
    Rodakiewicz, Henwar: 1936
    Rogoway, Marjorie: 1954, 1973
    Rohland, Paul & Caroline: 1915, 1949
    Ronnebeck, Arnold: 1934
    Roswell Museum and Art Center: 1974
    Rowntree, Leonard G.: 1938, 1940-1942, 1945, 1950, 1952-1954
    Santa Fe Festival of the Arts: 1978-1979
    Saunders, Sallie: 1953
    Saylor, Jeannette: 1978
    Schriever, George (The Anschutz Collection): 1973-1976
    Schwalbe, Diana: 1967, 1971, 1975, 1977
    Seres, Monique: 1970, 1973
    Shearer, Ivy: 1950, 1952, 1953
    Shearer, Augustus Hunt (Chuck) & Sally: 1957
    Simonson, Lee: 1914
    Simonson, Omar: 1914
    Slusser, Jean Paul: 1947, 1948
    Smith, Judson: 1952, 1953, 1956
    Solomon, Hyde: 1972
    Sternberg, Edward: 1943
    Stieglitz, Alfred: 1931
    Stokes, Mrs. Walter (Fanny): 1939-1944
    Stroh, Earl: 1948-1950, 1952, 1954
    Stuart, John: 1935
    Swaine, Ruth: 1945
    Swift, Florence Alston: 1928
    Swingle, W. W.: 1938, 1940, 1947, 1948
    Thompson, Shirley & Les: 1972, 1973
    Thompson, Vallie: 1954
    Trego, Charlotte: 1971-1978
    Trentham, Eugene (Steve): 1940, 1941, 1945
    Udell, Susan: 1978
    University of Delaware: 1974
    University of Kansas Museum of Art: 1973
    University of New Mexico: 1958
    Van Vechten, Carl: 1924, 1938
    Waldrum, Harold, 1971
    Walker, Maynard (Walker Galleries): 1941, 1942, 1947
    Walker, Bob & Mariella: 1971-1975, 1977
    Wardwell, Alice: 1951
    Watkins, Franklin: 1938, 1939
    Western Gallery of Fine Art: 1974
    Western States Arts Foundation: 1978
    White, Victor: 1939, 1941, 1943, 1944, 1974, 1977
    Whitney Museum of American Art: 1946, 1951, 1963, 1977, 1978
    Wiegand, Margarith: 1910
    Wilson, Kathy: 1951
    Wister, Frances A.: 1940
    Wister, Owen: 1933-1936, 1938-1940, 1942, 1948-1952, 1955
    Wister, Mrs. W. R.: 1937, 1940
    Wolman, Cecil & Leo: 1947, 1949, 1971, 1972, 1974, 1976, 1977
    Woodstock Artists Association, Inc.: 1975, 1977
    Woodstock Weekly: 1924
    Wright, Alice Morgan: 1928, 1938
    Wurlitzer, Helene: 1954
    Yaple, Dixie Lee: 1948
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, circa 1906-1908 June; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1908 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1908 August; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1908 October-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1908 December; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, circa 1909 January 1-12; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1909 January 1-14; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1909 February 1-6; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1909 February 7-14; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1909 February 8-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 January; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 February-March 1; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 May-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 July-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 September 1-14; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 September 15-30; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 October-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1910 December; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1911 January; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1911 February-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1911 April-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1912 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1912 April-July; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1912 August-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1912 October-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1913 January-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1913 June-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1913 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914 May; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914 August-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914 September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914 October-November; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1915 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1915 April-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1915 June-July; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1915 August; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1915 September-October; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1916; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1917 May-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1918 January-February; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1918 March-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1914 January-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1919-1929, 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1921; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, 1922-1926; 1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence with Grace Mott Johnson, Undated Letters, circa 1906-1940; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence with Nancy Lane, 1928 August-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence with Nancy Lane, 1928 October; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence with Nancy Lane, 1928 November; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence with Nancy Lane, Undated Letters, circa 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1935 March; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1935 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1935 April; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1935 June; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1935 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1936 January-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1936 May; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1936 June; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1936 July; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1943; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1947; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, 1950-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence with Marina Wister Dasburg, Undated Letters, circa 1935-1954; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1914; 1919-1925; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1926-1927; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1928-1929; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1929; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1931-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1933-1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1936-1938; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1939-1942; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1943-1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1945-1946; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1947-1950; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1951-1955; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, 1957-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence with Alfred Dasburg, Undated Letters, circa 1914-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence, 1909-1924; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - General Correspondence, 1926-1928; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - General Correspondence, 1929-1930; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 1931-1932; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - General Correspondence, 1933; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - General Correspondence, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - General Correspondence, 1934; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - General Correspondence, 1935; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - General Correspondence, 1936; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - General Correspondence, 1937 January-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - General Correspondence, 1937 May-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - General Correspondence, 1937 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - General Correspondence, 1938 January-February; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 1938 April-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 1939 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 1939 April-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 1940 January-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 1940 June-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 1941 January-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 1941 June-September; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 1941 October-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 1942 January-March; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 1942 April-June; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 1942 August-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 1943 January-April; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 1943 May-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 1944; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1945 January-May; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 1945 June-August; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, 1945 September-December; Archival Resource Key (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 1946-1951; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 4, Folder 19-27)
    - General Correspondence, 1952-1958; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 4, Folder 28-34)
    - General Correspondence, 1959-1973; Archival Resource Key; (7 folders) (Box 5, Folder 1-7)
    - General Correspondence, 1974-1979; Archival Resource Key; (9 folders) (Box 5, Folder 8-16)
    - General Correspondence, Undated Letters, A-H, circa 1910-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, Undated Letters, K-W, circa 1910-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, Unidentified Correspondents, circa 1910-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Writings, circa 1940s-1979; 1.3; Archival Resource Key
    Writings by Andrew Dasburg include two brief essays on painting and an essay on abstract art entitled "Notes for a Criticism" that he wrote for the Harwood Foundation in 1953. Writings by others include poetry written by Peggy Church, sent to Dasburg for Christmas over several years, one of which is entitled "Andrew's Tree in the Moonlight", as well as poems and song lyrics written by Dasburg's wife, Marina Wister Dasburg. Filed here are writings and research notes by Teles Romero's on the conditions of the Jicarilla Apaches Indian reservation, a topic of particular interest to Marina Dasburg. Also found are draft writings by Virginia Gardner for her book, Friend and Lover: The Life of Louise Bryant. Andrew Dasburg and Grace Mott Johnson were friends with Bryant and Andrew and Alfred Dasburg assisted Gardner in her research for the book. Additional research material compiled by Gardner and found here includes photocopies of news clippings and articles on Bryant.
    Writings about Andrew Dasburg consist of a portion of an essay by Howard Cook, a biographical essay about Dasburg by Mary Carroll Nelson, an essay by Mabel Dodge Luhan regarding Dasburg's mural at the Colorado Springs Art Centre, and an essay regarding Dasburg's artwork by Van Deren Coke. There is also a document in German possibly written by Dasburg's grandfather, and other notes by unidentified authors. Folders are arranged by author and items are arranged chronologically within each folder.
    - Writings by Andrew Dasburg, 1953, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Peggy Church, Poetry for Andrew Dasburg, 1950s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Marina Wister Dasburg, Miscellaneous Writings, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Gardner, Draft Writings and Research Material on Louise Bryant, circa 1972-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Mary Carroll Nelson, Essay about Andrew Dasburg, 1978-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Teles R. Romero, Writings and Research on Indians of Jicarilla Apaches, circa 1940s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Writings about Andrew Dasburg, 1959-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Writings and Notes by Others, circa 1970s; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Printed Material, 1922-1980; 1.4; Archival Resource Key
    Printed material concerns Dasburg's career, as well as his interest and participation in art events in New Mexico. Found here are three books, two specifically on artists in Taos, and one written by Dasburg's friend, Mabel Dodge Luhan. Other materials include exhibition announcements and catalogs for various group shows featuring artists of New Mexico, as well as solo exhibitions of Dasburg's work and the work of others. News clippings are about Dasburg, Taos news and art community, art exhibitions, and articles about his friends and family. Also found are newsletters from various New Mexico art organizations, blank postcards, some of which depict Woodstock, New York, a few press releases for exhibitions, and various programs and brochures. Items are arranged chronologically within each folder.
    - Books, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
      - Nordfeldt the Painter, Van Deren Coke, 1972; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Taos and Its Artists, Mabel Dodge Luhan, 1947; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - A Taos Mosaic, Claire Morrill, 1973; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Exhibition Announcements and Invitations, 1967-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1947-1977; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 32-33)
    - News Clippings, 1922-1959; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 34-35)
    - News Clippings, 1960-1979; Archival Resource Key; (2 folders) (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - News Clippings, Undated, circa 1922-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters, 1936, 1973-1979; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Programs and Brochures, 1941-1968, 1979; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Press Releases, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Postcards (Blank), circa 1920s, 1950s; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Material, circa 1950s-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, circa 1900-1978; 1.5; Archival Resource Key
    There are photographs of Andrew Dasburg and his family, friends, colleagues, homes, and artwork. Photographs of Dasburg include portraits and candid photographs. A few particularly noteworthy photographs depict Dasburg painting on Monhegan Island, Maine, in 1913; outside of Mabel Dodge Luhan's cottage in Provincetown, Massachusetts; outside of Luhan's home in Taos, New Mexico; and painting in his studio in Taos. Photographs of Dasburg with friends and family include him with his mother and son, Alfred; in a group photograph of Birge Harrison's Art Students' League summer class in Woodstock, New York, in 1907 along with his future wife, Grace Mott Johnson; in his studio at 115 rue Notre Dame des Champs with friends in 1910; with Konrad Cramer and John Reed in 1914; with artist Charles Kassler in Colorado; and with other unidentified groups of people, probably in Woodstock, NY. Also found are photographs of his son Alfred as a child and with his wife and children; photographs of friend and fellow artist Lila Wheelock Howard; and photographs of the Wister children, including Dasburg's third wife, Marina Wister. Notable among the photographs of family and friends include snapshots of Florence Lucius, Konrad and Florence Ballin Cramer, Frieda and D. H. Lawrence, and Mabel Dodge Luhan.
    The papers also include several photographs taken at Taos, New Mexico, including two photographs of Andrew and Alfred Dasburg with Tony Luhan and a photograph of Alfred with Mary Foote, Mabel Dodge Luhan, and Tony Luhan en route to a snake dance. Additional photographs of Taos include Native American events, landscapes, and architecture. Photographs of places include Dasburg's house in Woodstock, New York, his mother's house in Wurtsboro, New York, Monhegan Island, Nova Scotia, and other unidentified places. Also found are photographs and slides of artwork by Dasburg and a few photographs of artwork by others. Folders are arranged by subject and chronologically within each folder.
    - Photographs of Andrew Dasburg, 1908-1970s; Archival Resource Key; (4 folders) (Box 6, Folder 9-12)
    - Photographs of Andrew Dasburg with Friends & Family, circa 1910-1976; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Photographs of Alfred Dasburg & Family, circa 1912-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Photographs of Lila Wheelock Howard, circa 1910s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Photographs of Wister Children, circa 1902; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Photographs of Friends and Family, 1914-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Photographs of Taos, New Mexico, 1920s-1930s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Photographs of Models, circa 1920s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Photographs of Nudes (Possibly Rose Davidson), 1911; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Unidentified Photographs of People, circa 1900-1960, Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Photographs of Dasburg House in Woodstock, New York, circa 1920; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Photographs of Monhegan Island, 1913; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Photographs of Nova Scotia, circa 1910s; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Photograps of Places, circa 1900-1960; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Photographs of Animals, circa 1910s; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Photographs of Andrew Dasburg/Grace Mott Johnson Exhibition, 1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Photographs of Artwork by Dasburg, circa 1950s-1970s; Archival Resource Key; (3 folders; not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 28-30)
    - Photographs of Artwork by Others, circa 1914-1970s; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Slides, Photographs of Andrew Dasburg, 1948, 1956, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Slides, Photographs of Artwork by Dasburg, 1977-1978; Archival Resource Key; (Not scanned) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Artwork, undated; 1.6; Archival Resource Key
    Artwork by Andrew Dasburg includes three woodblock prints of "Girl with Yo-Yo" and two small drawings.
    - Artwork by Andrew Dasburg, undated; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Alfred Dasburg Papers, 1914-1980; 1.7; Archival Resource Key